I'm scared!
So,
what we're going to do today is
double speed dance.
We're going to challenge it.
Double speed dance?
It's easy.
I'm getting used to double speed dance.
Shoo!
It's easy.
I think I can do it.
You can do it, too.
I want to do something more exciting.
You are good at it.
Thank you.
I was the first one to be picked.
I have a lot of time.
I want to challenge 2.5 times faster.
The next wall.
I see.
2.5 times faster.
Minami is easy.
I'm not.
We are excited to go over the wall.
Let's go over the wall.
I want to go over the wall.
Let's go.
Let's go together.
I'm Natsume.
Let's start.
We are going to do Cupid in Love.
That's important.
Let's dance.
Let's listen to it.
You can do it!
This program is
a program where the members of the same
age group
challenge various things
and raise their competitiveness.
Music start!
Yui Kashiwaguchi
Yu with Kabuki
What on earth is going on?
That's our song!
This is our song!
Teacher covering
纏 işler
Phone call
ild send
I'll send
Ooo
way
Hmmm
Na.
My goodness, can someone answer me?
Who is this?
I understand what your problem.
Help me!
Y been evaded
Y
Yaya
Naturally
Y B been evaded
Everyone
Everything
Y Opened
Japanese
OK
Cheers
I'm not doing it!
It was so easy.
It was so fun.
We did it.
I'm so happy.
Thank you.
The next is the last one.
Let's watch it.
It was so easy.
I think it was good.
Let's watch it.
Please.
Music, start!
Stop, stop.
I know.
The song is so short.
She is shaking!
She is한데 it's been a long time.
Well….
Seriously this dance is what is kinda
dangerous
I can't handle this
Fan signing event can be found here
I'm dancing.
I can't see the left side.
I'm taking a picture.
Thank you for watching.
What are you doing?
I can't remember.
It's going to burn soon.
lol
It was insane.
We did it!
We all did it!
I was like, what were we doing?
It was so quick that I didn't know what
we were doing.
It was really quick.
We still have a lot of training to do.
We will try a lot of things and we will
go through this wall together.
Thank you for watching!
I'm going to play the rainbow piano
What's wrong?
When I smile,
the world seems to be shining.
I can turn the umbrella to be relaxed.
I can't walk without it.
Someone is crying somewhere.
If you like this video,
if you think it's cute,
or if you want to push the button,
please subscribe to our channel and
click the bell button!
Please!
Please leave comments too!
Thank you for watching!
Subbed by Dreadopp and Zedopp.
Sayonara Goodbye to me of yesterday
The city lights after the rain sparkle
My heart is like a sunny day
I play the sound of a puddle
I play the rainbow piano
Sayonara Goodbye to me of yesterday
Goodbye to me of yesterday
The city after the rain is sparkling
My heart is like a flower
Tears are blinding me
I'll wear a rainbow dress